BGM
Hello, this is Yamaguchi from TAP99. Today, I would like to show you a special project using youtube to introduce a camera that I have just acquired.
First of all, here is the camera.
It is the ZONE Leica Q3.
I would like to open it up.
Then, the door.
Then, the door,
Like this. noise town SD única enенные.
This way.
I mean, the design is ridiculously cool.
And the performance is amazing.
And the price is amazing.
Specs and all.
If you look it up, you'll find it.
Various people have introduced it.
I thought it would be better to check them out.
I'd like to introduce you to some of the people who came to the Tap editorial department
This is the Leica Q3 that came to our editorial department.
I'd like to introduce the Leica Q3 to you.
I thought a normal review would be boring.
I thought it would be boring to do a normal review.
I thought it would be boring to just do a normal review of the Leica Q3.
or a website specializing in cameras
or a website that specializes in cameras
I think they are talking about the greatness of the specs.
I'm wondering if we can do a project that only we can do
I was wondering if we could do a project that only we can do.
A while ago, we had a project with an idol group called Team Shachi
an idol group from Nagoya
I was given an opportunity to do an interview with them
I had the opportunity to interview them for the first time in a while.
It's been a while since I've had a chance to do an interview with them, and I had some fun and interesting conversations.
The article was published the other day, and I was very happy to see that quite a few people read it.
If you haven't seen the article yet, please take a look at the link in the summary section.
In fact, during the interview, I was able to use the Q3 as a tool to find out how amazing Leica really is, and to learn about the performance of the camera itself.
I wanted to find out what kind of performance this camera itself has. I wanted to know what it would be like if someone who is used to taking pictures and being taken pictures, rather than someone who loves cameras, actually took a camera and took pictures.
I wanted to see how they would use the camera and how they would use it.
I asked the girls to do a little filming project for me, and I put together a little video, so please take a look at it!
Please take a look.
Today, I'm going to ask each of you to take a picture of a member of the group using a cohort.
We would like you to take pictures of one person or another.
May I take pictures in this order? Yes, ma'am.
Okay, grandma...
Let grandma take the pictures.
Okay, go ahead.
Okay, let's do it.
Take a picture, take a picture.
Shoot where?
Mags.
I like this, I like this, I like this, I like this.
I like this, this, this.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
this one is a member and this one too
This one is cute too.
Right?
Music
Oh, it's leaking so much.
It's so beautiful.
We're waiting for you.
Such a beautiful shot.
I'd like to sell them for 250,000 yen each.
You want it to be worth it.
Then I'll do my best.
Idols don't take pictures.
Do you think this camera is worth a million yen?
Totally.
I've never spent half a million before.
Do you see any difference between this and an iPhone?
I mean, look at the iPhone.
You don't have to worry about the light.
Or the direction of the sun.
It's beautiful everywhere.
I thought it would be too dark.
I thought it would be too dark, but it brightens it up so much.
I hope the shadows aren't too obnoxious.
Yeah, it's not.
It's like art.
It's amazing.
And quiet.
Art.
And the focus is good on its own, so that's nice.
Like this.
Oh, yeah.
I've had it now for, like, two years.
Two years, I think.
We can only buy it two years from now?
Only we can buy it now.
But, I mean, who's going to buy it?
Who's buying now? Is it a job?
Work.
Camera enthusiasts.
Yes, camera enthusiasts.
I feel like, horizontally, you're holding this over your shoulder.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Dangerous!
Brand fucking shit!
I like this symbol.
But don't you want it?
I want it.
I didn't know they made them like this.
I'm glad to know that.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
They had a lot of fun taking pictures.
They were very happy with the pictures they took and said they were very beautiful.
As for the photos we took this time
TAP99's web media also has a feature article on the photos taken this time.
If you'd like to see the photos more closely, please take a look at the article
If you want to see the photos more clearly, please take a look at the article on TAP99's website.
The Q3 itself is of high quality, and the autofocus is very good.
I thought it was capable of taking beautiful photos.
I think it is a good camera that even people who are not used to using it can easily take pictures with it.
As I said in the video, the price is high, so
It's not for the super rich beginner photographer.
or if you want to take photos that are a bit different from iPhone photos.
I would recommend this camera to those who want to take photos that are a bit different from those taken with an iPhone.
That's all for this video.
Thank you for watching until the end!
We would be very happy if you like, comment and subscribe to our channel!
See you in the next video!
Bye bye!
Have a good night!
Please subscribe to our channel!